





SUMMARY OF SKILLS

- Self-motivated software engineer with a passion for developing products that have real-world impact
- One year of industry experience in software development with two co-op terms
- SFU CS and BCIT CST grad with strong programming skills specializing in web development

Programming Languages: Java, Python, C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Ruby, C, Swift, PHP

Tools/IDE: Git, MySQL, JIRA, Jenkins, TeamCity, Eclipse, Android Studio, XCode, Visual Studio

Frameworks: React & Redux, Flask, AngularJS, Ruby on Rails, Node.js, Django, ASP.NET, Laravel

EDUCATION

Simon Fraser University

Jan 2017 - Dec 2019

• Bachelor of Science, Major in Computer Science

British Columbia Institute of Technology

Jan 2014 – Dec 2017

- Diploma of Computer Systems Technology (Web and Mobile Option)
- Graduated with Distinction, GPA: 88%

INDUSTRY EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Intern – CA Technologies | Vancouver, BC

May 2018 - Aug 2018

- Worked extensively with React & Redux to develop features for the front-end team
- Automated the workflow processes for all the front-end Git PRs by developing a TeamCity script which resulted in improved team productivity
- Developed a feature flagging framework that is used for all the front-end projects
- Contributed to daily agile scrum meetings, code reviews, technical documentation, and sprint planning

Software Developer Intern – Ayogo Health | Vancouver, BC

Sept 2017 – Dec 2017

- Collaborated with the product, UX, QA, and development teams to design and develop a feature complete health app in AngularJS
- Developed reusable front-end components for AngularJS to be used in future health apps
- Designed data models and integrated them with RESTful JSON APIs for the Rails backend server
- Unit tested and versioned front-end components on npm

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Cradle – React & Redux and Flask Project | Demo: cradle-app.herokuapp.com/login

- A web and mobile app that digitizes and replaces the medical paper system generated by the Cradle VSA device
- Featured in <u>SFU news</u> and selected best project by the client out of an entire class to be further implemented and deployed for industry use in Uganda
- Developed majority of the React & Redux front-end, Flask back-end features, and MySQL database schema

Mystudygroup - Ruby on Rails Project | Demo: mystudygroup.herokuapp.com

- A platform that connects students who want to find a study group by utilizing Google Maps API
- Designed, developed, and deployed a Ruby on Rails web app using Heroku, Redis, PostgreSQL, and Amazon S3
- Contributed to over 90% of code to create a fully featured, tested, and polished web app

Animal-dex - Django Project | Demo: animal-dex.herokuapp.com

- A web app that hosts information for 1000+ animals which were scraped from Wikipedia using a Python script
- Utilized Wiki API and Beautiful Soup to aggregate data for the PostgreSQL database